Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files 1876-
24-04-3326
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine
30.5 cubic ft.
Alumni biographical files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Biographical files of graduates of the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine was founded in 1894. It was originally called the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Biographical files of graduates of the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. College of Veterinary Medicine.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.; Cornell University. Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
Veterinarians; Universities and colleges. Alumni and alumnae.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Records of living alumni of the college are restricted to use by college staff only. Records of deceased alumni are open for research.
HISTORY OF OWNERSHIP
The history of this collection is uncertain. Much of it was created by the college Alumni Association, but it was added to by the College Library staff as well. Other material may have been added from other sources.
SERIES LIST
Series I. 1871-1899
Box 1
Series II. 1900-1999
Boxes 1-29
1900-1909
1910-1919
1920-1929
1930-1939
1940-1949
1950-1959
1960-1969
1970-1979
1980-1989
1990-1999
Series III. 2000-2011
Box 29
2000-2011
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. 1871-1899
  - Farrington, Arthur Manly, BVS '79, DVM '03, 1879 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    18??-1931
    No class photo
  - Kilborne, Fred Lucius, BVS '85, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    1859-1936
    No class photo; Includes photographs
    See also Collection #1806, Kilborne, Fred Lucius papers, 1884-1936
  - Meiners, Rudolph F., 1896 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    18??-1959
    No class photo; No record of Cornell DVM degree
  - Howe, Walter Emerson, DVM '97, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    1871-1950
  - Ryder, Herman Reeve, DVM '97, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1869-1948
  - Weihe, Walter Edward, DVM '97, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1869-
  - Dustan, Henry Winfield, DVM '98, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1876-1944
    See also Collection #37-05-3378, Dustan, Henry W. Veterinary Class Notebook, 1897
  - Kelly, Albert Boulware, DVM '98, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    1876-1915
  - Lehrman, Henry John, DVM '98, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    1878-1909?
  - Stanclift, Ray Jones, DVM '98, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    1874-1956
  - Fish, Pierre Augustine, DVM '99, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    1865-1931
    See College Deans folder - Was Cornell Veterinary College dean from 1929 to 1932
    See also Collection #24-02-1677, Fish, Pierre Augustine papers, 1890-1931
  - Gay, Carl Warren, DVM '99, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    1877-
  - Illston, Henry Wright, DVM '99, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    1874-1901
  - Perkins, Chester Ransom, DVM '99, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    1875-1957
  - Potter, Charles Beecher, DVM '99, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1872-1916
  - Scammel, Floyd Gage, DVM '99, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    1867-1939
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1900-1909
    - Barnes, Clarence Lyon, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      1875-1953
    - Corrigan, John W., 1900 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      1868-1932
    - Hopkins, Grant Sherman, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      1865-1952
      No class photo; See also Faculty file
    - Jewell, Charles Henry, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      1869-1929
    - Juliand, Louis, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      1876-1965
      Includes photographs
    - Mitchell, William John, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      1876-1950
    - Stone, Garry Terrell, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      1877-1948
    - Fish, Harry Spaulding, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      18??-1960
    - Fisher, Carl Wallace, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      1871-1935
    - Flocken, Charles Frederick, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      1876-1951
    - Gallagher, Bernard Alfred, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      1881-1940
    - Kanstoroom, David Salmon, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Reed, Raymond Clinton, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      1868-1940
    - Shaw, Clarence Earl, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      1874-1957
    - Udall, Denny Hammond, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      1874-1955
      See also Faculty file and Collection #6641, Udall, D.H., papers, 1902-1930
    - Ward, Archibald Robinson, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      1875-1946
      See also Collection #6596. Ward, Archibald R. papers, 1919-1914
    - Wilder, Joseph Lot, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      1876-1939
    - Beebe, Harry Snyder, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      1878-1946
    - Burnett, Samuel Howard, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      1869-1928
      See also Faculty file
    - Bushnell, Fred Forbes, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      1878-1933
    - English, Burt, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      1878-1973?
    - Foster, Robert Julian, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      1880-
      See also Collection #6549, Foster, Robert J. papers, 1894-1958
    - Holford, Fred Dewitt, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      1878-1948
    - Knapp, John B., 1902 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      1875-1943
    - Lueder, Charles Augustus, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      1878-1954
    - Reidy, John Bernard, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      1877-1959
    - Rosenthal, Jerome Walter, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      1880-1942
    - Davenport, Miles LeRoy, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      1869-1938
    - Fehr, Frederic Frank, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      1876-1974
    - Hughes, Davis Arthur, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      1870-1917
    - LeFevre, Daniel DuBois, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      1874-1932
    - Loomis, Francis James, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      1882-1928
    - Millen, Charles James, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      1881-
    - Miner, George Harry, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      1879-1975
    - Simons, Fred Bertrand, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 53)
      1875-1920
    - Smith, Ernest Ireland J., 1903 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      1874-1925
    - Stroud, Bert Brenette, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      18??-1918
    - Wilbur, Bert Raymond, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      1876-1957
    - Zimmer, Ludo Little, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 57)
      1877-1951
    - Beebe, Ward Losee, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 58)
      1881-1957
    - Cady, Bert James, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      1882-1966
    - Day, Clarence Finch, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 60)
      1879-1931
    - Fernandez, Alberto Camelo, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 61)
      1878-1951
      From South America (Brazil and Argentina)
    - Gallagher, John Joseph, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 62)
      1876-1916
    - Gibbs, Charles E., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 63)
      1878-1944
    - Haring, Clarence Melvin, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 64)
      Was dean at Univ.of California Vet College (1947-48)
    - Knapp, Valentine Mott, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 65)
      1875-1940
    - Mack, Winfred Berdell, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 66)
      1871-1918
    - Madden, John Alden, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 67)
      1877-1907
    - McNamara, John Aloysius, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 68)
      1879-1961
      Includes First Annual Banquet program
    - Milks, Howard Jay, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 69)
      1879-1954
    - O'Campo, Vincente, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 70)
      1881-1935
      From Argentina
    - Seaman, Arthur M., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 71)
      1878-1964
    - Tiffany, John Blakeslee, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 72)
      1876-
    - Walmsley, Fred Dowling, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 73)
      1882-1948
    - Andrews, Frederick Willment, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 74)
      1882-1964
    - Axtell, Percy Jay, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 75)
      1880-1961
    - Backus, Newell D., 1905 (Box 1, Folder 76)
      1889-1954
    - Baker, Frank James, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 77)
      1873-1941
    - Brockett, Arthur Andrew, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 78)
      1884-1956
      See also Collection #6983m, Brockett, Arthur A. veterinary miscellany, 1929-1930
    - Buffington, Ralph Maurice, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 79)
      1880-1933
    - Burley, Arthur James, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 80)
      1879-1958
    - Dean, Arlton Knickerbocker, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 81)
      1880-1943
    - Dimock, William Wallace, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 82)
      1880-1953
      Was AVMA president (1941-42)
    - English, Andrew, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Gannett, Ray Willard, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 84)
      1882-1954
    - Hamilton, Melancthon, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 85)
      187?-1939
    - Lawrence, Howard Leslie, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 86)
      1881-1953
    - Linch, Charles, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 87)
      1875-1944
    - Mason, Alfred Lewis, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 88)
      1882-1974?
    - McNair, Frederick Henry, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 89)
      1872-
    - Pendergast, Walter Michael, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 90)
      1883-
    - Smith, Fletcher Eugene, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 91)
      1876-1959
    - Snyder, Harold Jay, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 92)
      1883-1939
    - Taylor, Charles Henry, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 93)
      1873-1936
    - Thompson, Mulford Conklin, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 94)
      1876-1952
    - Traum, Jacob, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Treman, John Walter, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 96)
      1883-1954
    - Weaver, Philip Victor, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 97)
      1879-1947
    - Whiting, Rex A. 1906, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 98)
      1884-1937
    - York, Fritz Elera (Elerd?), 1905 (Box 1, Folder 99)
      1872-1910
    - Backus, Lee Selden, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 100)
      1883-1959
    - Baldwin, Charles Ruben, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Chamberlain, Frank Wilbut, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 102)
      1877-1952
    - Eggleston, William Seymour, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 103)
      1873-1921
    - Fagundes, Adaberto A., 1906 (Box 1, Folder 104)
      1885-1934
      From Sao Paulo, Brazil
    - Foster, Franklin Luther, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 105)
      1882-
    - Gallagher, Francis Leo, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 106)
      1885-1928
    - Giltner, Leigh T., 1906 (Box 1, Folder 107)
      1884-1955
    - Giltner, Ward, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 108)
      1882-1950
    - Herron, Wallace Wood, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 109)
      1881-1919
    - Hills, John Vernon, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Johnson, John Arthur, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Little, Elbert Warfield, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 112)
      1883-1938
    - Maloney, Alfred Joseph, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 113)
      1881-1934
    - McCarthy, Thomas Alfred, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 114)
      1883-1931
    - McGinnis, Ralph Wyllie, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 115)
      1882-1932
    - Merry, Albert Edmun, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 116)
      1885-1961
    - Miller, John Fred, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 117)
      1879-1959
    - Nelligan, Walter, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 118)
      1884-1921
    - Roadhouse, Chester Linwood, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 119)
      1881-1969
    - Simpson, Ernest Lee, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      1882-1940
    - Smith, William Burritt, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      1887-1936
    - Stafford, Rosslyn John, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      1883-1910
    - Sullivan, Eugene Joseph, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      1870-1952
    - Taylor, Walter Jennings, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      1877-1931
    - Wills, John Gordon, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      1879-1974
    - Wright, Frank Henry, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      1883-1974?
    - Burns, John Robert, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      1881-1945
    - Chase, George Rawley, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      1881-1959
    - Clark, William Lowellyn, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      1883-1940
    - Cleaver, Fred Everett, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      1882-1944
    - Cogswell, Walter Kingman, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      1886-1910
    - Darby, Robert Neil Gordon, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      1885-1957
    - Drew, John Bragg, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      1878-1966
    - Eastman, D. K., 1907 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      1884-1944
    - Eno, Charles Rudd, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      1884-1953
    - Frink, Walter E., 1907 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      1878-1962
    - Frost, James Nathan, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      1885-1949
      See also Faculty file and Collection #24-2-1204, Frost, James Nathan, papers, 1898-1907
    - Gilbert, Walter Levi, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      1878-1960
    - Gilyard, Arthur Thomas, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      1886-1946
    - Hyatt, Bradford A., 1907 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      1881-1968
    - Keith, Arthur Raymond, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      1882-1974
    - Knight, Ralph Floyd, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      1884-1960
    - Lewis, Watson F., 1907 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      1882-1949
    - Morehouse, Walter Gould, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      1877-1935
    - Newman, William "Dusty" Seymour, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Was "one of Cornell's all-time athletes" while attending veterinary college
    - Prucha, Joseph Vit, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      1882-1919
    - Rood, Vaughn Wesley, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Sharp, Vern Adolphus, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      1886-
    - Sheldon, Thomas A., 1907 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      18??-
    - Thomson, Charles Goff, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      1883-1936
    - Tillou, Harris Baker, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      1886-1932
    - Town, Clarence Adelbert, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      1885-1937
    - Wallace, James Garfield, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      1885-1943
    - Watkins, Robert Eugene, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Way, Cassius, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      1881-1948
      Was AVMA president (1939-40)
    - Weller, Bryon McNeil, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      1882-1913
    - Willson, Frederic Cornelius, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      1883-1971
    - Wood, Frederick William, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      1881-1955
    - Boynton, William Hutchins, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Case, Leonard Newton, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      1881-1971
    - Case, Lloyd Everett, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Davie, Leon Clifton, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      1884-1952
    - Edmonds, Alfred Benjamin, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      1887-1923
    - Hall, Arthur George, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Hyde, Roger Davies, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      1882-1959
      Photos of foot-and-mouth disease eradication
    - Jackson, Edwin Ruthven, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      1888-1966
    - Kimball, Victor Gage, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      1884-1927
    - Marshall, Charles William, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      1882-1939
    - Oderkirk,Charles Clayton, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      1884-1964
      See also Collection #37-5-3410, Oderkirk, Charles C. Cornell scrapbook, 1904-1907
    - Pearce, Charles Darius, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      1882-1961
    - Polk, Leroy Vanderpool, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      1888-
    - Shattuck, Byron Smith, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Smith, Clyde Edwin, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Sunderville, Earl, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      1886-1958
    - Van Orman, Ray, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      1884-1954
    - Wheeler, Lloyd Anthony, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      1882-1921
    - Bell, John Benson, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      1886-1936
    - Bell, Ralph M., 1909 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      1897-1933
    - Bennett, Walter Didama, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      1881-1943?
    - Benson, Luther Joseph, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 61)
      1888-1938
    - Schalberg, Alfred M., 1909 (Box 2, Folder 62)
      188?-1913
    - Stephenson, Roy Lindsay, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      1886-1943
    - Townsend, John Vincent, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 64)
      1883-1932
    - Trainor, Owen Francis, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Welch, Howard, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Wood, Frank Sidney, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      1886-1965
    - Woodside, James Hamlet, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      188?-1932
  - 1910-1919
    - Aiken, Howard Kelsey, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 69)
      1885-
    - Denman, Irving Olney, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      1887-1975
    - Doll, Curtis Emery, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      1884-1942
    - Dooling, Maurice John, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      1885-1964
    - Dowd, Frederick Fitzgerald, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 73)
      1888-1976?
    - Dunham, Le Verne, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 74)
      1887-1945
    - Evans, Maurice Edward Joseph, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      1888-1933
    - Fairchild, Charles Radcliffe, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      1886-1912
    - Fernandez, G. C., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      Class photo only; From South America?
    - Frederick, Harry, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      1889-1925
    - Ham, Lynn W., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Howes, Murray, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 80)
      1887-1952
    - Kimball, Florence, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 81)
      1885-1947
      Includes various photographs
      First woman graduate and first woman DVM in US
    - Lown, Morton, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Matthews, Lewis Sheridan, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 83)
      1889-1918
    - Moore, Audrey D., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 84)
      1884-1958
    - Munsell, Warren Adsitt, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 85)
      1876-1918
    - Overton, Floyd C., Jr., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 86)
      1888-1947
    - Parker, Leon Luther, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 87)
      1886-1957
    - Roig, Chester Austin, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 88)
      188?-1968
    - Slawson [Schlesinger, Jr.], Alexander, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 89)
      Name change from: Alexander Schlesinging, Jr.
    - Stark, Abraham Maurice, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 90)
      1887-1951
    - Thompson, Erastus G., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 91)
      1883-1961
    - Wheeler, George Waterbur, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 92)
      1886-1933
    - Banks, Ray Steere, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 93)
      1889-1957
      See also Collection #6574, Banks, Ray S. papers 1909-1910
    - Boyce, Walter, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 94)
      1886-1955
    - Breed, Frank, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 95)
      1886-1961
    - Buencamino, Victor Abreu, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 96)
      From Philippines
    - Burleigh, William Forrest, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 97)
      1887-
    - Combs, Arthur Wright, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 98)
      1889-1974
    - Corbin, Cecil Issiac, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 99)
      1887-1958
    - Danforth, Arthur Lewis, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Danziger, Max, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Deal, John Ellis, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 102)
      1888-1974?
    - Fitch, Clifford Penny, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 103)
      1884-1940
      Was AVMA President (1933-34)
    - Fritz, Walter E., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 104)
      1887-1967
    - Gregory, Emory I., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 105)
      1890-1955
    - Jones, Carl Ives, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 106)
      1885-1962
    - Krohn, Lester D., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 107)
      1888-1977?
    - Meador, Daniel John, Jr., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 108)
      1888-19??
    - Millard, Hugh Robinson, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 109)
      1886-1918
    - Mitchell, James Francis, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 110)
      1884-1972?
    - Morris, Charles Eugene, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 111)
      1887-1961
    - Noback, Charles Victor, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 112)
      1888-1937
    - Painton, Edward F., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 113)
      1885-1933
    - Pickens, Earl Max, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Rowe, Roy P., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 115)
      1887-1964
    - Rubio, Antonio Jesus, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 116)
      From Cuba
    - Shaul, Kenneth Adams, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 117)
      1887-1968
    - Simms, Robert, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 118)
      1887-1954
    - Stevens, Guy Gross, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 119)
      1888-1962
    - Vail, Irving R., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 120)
      1889-1960
    - Williams, Albert E., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 121)
      1890-1924
    - Birch, Raymond Russell, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 122)
      See also Faculty file and Collection #24-2-525, Birch, Raymond Russell, papers, 1910-1958
    - Bolton, Rudolph Ray, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 123)
      Inlcudes various photographs
    - Bosshart, John K., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      1884-1962
    - Buck, Walter Clark, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      1888-1958
    - Butts, Emmett K., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      1885-1915
    - Cohen, Jacob Harvey, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      1889-
    - Curd, Kirksey Louis, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      First African-American graduate
    - Dean, Harmon Gregory, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Flanagan, Russell J., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Forsyth, Arthur J., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      1892-1958
    - Gleason, Willard Sherman, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      1889-1964
    - Grace, Arthur Cecil, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      1890-
    - Jennings, Earl Andrews, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      1888-1936
    - Koten, Louis Raphael, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      1884-1939
    - Markham, Earl Simeon, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      See also Collection #37-05-3359, Markham, Earl S. papers, 1908-1938, bulk 1912-1919
    - McClelland, Alfred Honeywell, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      1890-1977
    - Merchant, Eustace S. D., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      1887-1974
      Philippino background
    - O'Loughlin, Daniel, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      1890-1972
    - Orth, Melvin Auringer, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      1891-1974
    - Pelton, L. Cleveland, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      1886-1974
    - Roberts, James Flanders, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      1889-1972
    - Scott, Robert Hubbard, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Shaw, Richard Nutting, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      1889-1961
    - Sullivan, Michael Wallace, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Tompkins, Leland James, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Webber, Orrin Blake, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      1890-1953
    - Wermuth, John J., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      1888-1961
    - Wilson, Edward Lewis, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Wright, David E., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      1891-1919
    - Barker, Harry Elmer, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      1888-1952
    - Beach, Jerry Raymond, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      1888-1951
    - Brandenburg, Tunis Orville, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      1890-1961
    - Casey, John William, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      1890-1947
    - Clark, David William, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      1884-1919
    - Cook, Joseph Dwight, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      1891-1921
    - Feldman, Abraham, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      1892-1936
    - Freer, Archibald, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      1891-1941?
    - Goff, A. Cameron, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      1890-1984
    - Griffin, Charles Albert, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      1899-1955
    - Guile, Charles Russell, Jr., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      1889-1929
    - Keonig, Nathaniel Edward, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      1889-1955
    - McCord, Ralph Bemus, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      1890-1957
    - Morse, John Robertson, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      1889-1946
    - Muldoon, William Edward, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      1887-1935
    - Naylor, Howard Wing, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      1887-1969
    - Reed, Lewis Francis, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Selkin, William James, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      1891-1939
    - Stevenson, William Herbert, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      1890-1915
    - Thompsett, Glenn William, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      1886-1939
    - Wheat, John Chase, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      1889-1958
    - Wheelock, Benjamin Harris, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      1888-1945
    - Allen, David Boyce, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      1891-1918
    - Andrews, John Dewit, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      1888-1964
    - Baker, Harrison Vedder, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      1893-1957
    - Carnrite, James Schuyler, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      1892-1962
    - Clark, Joseph Stanley, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      1885-1968
    - Clarke, Harold, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      1892-1959
    - Dean, Stanley Louis, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 56)
      1889-1959
    - Deal, Alfred Freer, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      1891-
    - Dederick, Raymond Edgar, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Deming, David Francis, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      1885-1950
    - Eggleston, Harry William, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      1884-1943
    - Gardner, Clyde Armstrong, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      1889-1928
    - Gardner, Maurice Earl, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Goldberg, Samuel Alexander, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      1883-1964
    - Haner, Frank Henry, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      1890-1950